Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪
[The Sparrow's Gambit]
[مناورة العصفور]
[Episode 13]
[الحلقة 13]
Rumeng,
رومينج،
I know you've suffered many grievances
أعلم أنك عانيت من العديد من المظالم
since entering the Wang family.
منذ انضمامه إلى عائلة وانغ.
Set your mind at ease.
أريح بالك.
Once you are formally married,
بمجرد زواجك رسميًا،
I will protect you.
سأحميك.
Okay.
تمام.
Rumeng,
رومينج،
what's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Rumeng?
رومينج؟
Room 904. Have fun.
الغرفة 904. استمتع.
After tonight,
بعد الليلة،
you'll understand I'm better than her.
ستفهم أنني أفضل منها.
By now,
بحلول الآن،
she should already be with Mr. Li.
يجب أن تكون بالفعل مع السيد لي.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Wenbin.
وينبين.
Rumeng! Rumeng!
رومينج! رومينج!
Here I come, babe!
أنا قادم يا حبيبتي!
Come on, babe!
هيا يا حبيبتي!
With my strength alone,
بقوتي وحدها،
I could never expose their crimes.
لن أتمكن أبدًا من كشف جرائمهم.
Babe,
حبيبتي
here I come!
انا قادم هنا!
Mr. Wang.
السيد وانغ.
Mr. Li.
السيد لي.
So,
لذا،
did you enjoy yourself earlier?
هل استمتعت بوقتك في وقت سابق؟
Man,
رجل،
you really went all out.
لقد بذلت قصارى جهدك حقا.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
From now on, you can count on me
من الآن فصاعدا، يمكنك الاعتماد علي
for anything the Wang family needs.
لأي شيء تحتاجه عائلة وانج.
Mr. Li,
السيد لي،
then I would like
ثم أود
to thank you verbally.
لأشكرك لفظيًا.
I'll send you a generous package later.
سأرسل لك طردًا سخيًا لاحقًا.
We're all family now.
نحن جميعا عائلة الآن.
Wang Penghui, do you even see me as your daughter?
وانغ بينج هوي، هل ترى أنني ابنتك؟
You handed me over to someone else like livestock?
سلمتني لشخص آخر مثل الماشية؟
Are you even human?
هل أنت إنسان؟
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
haven't I done every dirty, difficult job
ألم أفعل كل الأعمال القذرة والصعبة؟
for the Wang family?
لعائلة وانغ؟
What are you talking about?
ماذا تتحدث عنه؟
You gave me
لقد أعطيتني
to such
لمثل هذا
an old scumbag?
رجل عجوز حقير؟
Mr. Wang,
السيد وانغ،
this is your daughter!
هذه ابنتك!
She can't just make wild accusations!
لا يمكنها أن تكتفي بإلقاء إتهامات جامحة!
She's slandering me in front of all these people!
إنها تشوه سمعتي أمام كل هؤلاء الناس!
You couldn't get back into the Chamber,
لم تتمكن من العودة إلى الغرفة،
so this is your pathetic move?
إذن هذه هي حركتك المثيرة للشفقة؟
Everyone, my conscience is clear.
الجميع، ضميري مرتاح.
I fear no false accusations.
لا أخشى أي اتهامات كاذبة.
This filthy woman must have
هذه المرأة القذرة يجب أن يكون لديها
been fooling around with some other man
لقد كنت أعبث مع رجل آخر
and now wants me to take the blame.
ويريدني الآن أن أتحمل اللوم.
Let me tell you,
دعني أخبرك،
dream on!
احلم!
Nonsense!
هراء!
You're all hypocrites!
أنتم جميعا منافقون!
So-called pillars of the business community!
ما يسمى بأعمدة مجتمع الأعمال!
You dare to do it but won't admit it, is that it?
أنت تجرؤ على القيام بذلك ولكنك لا تريد الاعتراف بذلك، أليس كذلك؟
Wan'er,
وانر،
could there be some misunderstanding?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك بعض سوء الفهم؟
You...
أنت...
Misunderstanding?
سوء الفهم؟
It should have been you!
كان ينبغي أن تكون أنت!
You arranged all of this!
لقد رتبت كل هذا!
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Guards!
حراس!
To think she'd stoop to outright violence!
أعتقد أنها ستنحدر إلى العنف الصريح!
Let me go!
دعني أذهب!
Mr. Wang,
السيد وانغ،
regarding today's incident...
بخصوص حادثة اليوم...
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Once the Military Governor Chen returns,
بمجرد عودة الحاكم العسكري تشين،
I will personally come to apologize.
سوف آتي شخصيا للاعتذار.
You've completely humiliated me today.
لقد أذللتني تمامًا اليوم.
Go home
اذهب إلى المنزل
and kneel
و اركع
until I am satisfied.
حتى أكون راضيا.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
So you're determined
لذلك أنت مصمم
to marry into the Wang family?
الزواج من عائلة وانغ؟
Yes.
نعم.
Please leave.
من فضلك أرحل.
Don't make me hate you.
لا تجعلني أكرهك.
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Rumeng.
رومينج.
What a farce today.
يا لها من مهزلة اليوم!
Yes.
نعم.
A farce.
مهزلة.
You weren't hurt, were you?
لم تصاب بأذى، أليس كذلك؟
No.
لا.
No...
لا...
That's good.
هذا جيد.
But there's something I want to ask you now.
ولكن هناك شيء أريد أن أسألك عنه الآن.
Where were you when Wan'er had her incident?
أين كنت عندما تعرضت وان إير للحادثة؟
Where was I?
أين كنت؟
Shouldn't you know best?
ألا يجب عليك أن تعرف الأفضل؟
Then why did I hear
ثم لماذا سمعت
Chen Wenbin was with you?
هل كان تشين وينبين معك؟
What was in the wine?
ماذا كان في النبيذ؟
You know perfectly well.
أنت تعرف ذلك جيدا.
What Marshal Chen was doing,
ما كان يفعله المارشال تشين،
and where he was...
وأين كان...
How would I, in my dazed state,
كيف يمكنني، في حالتي المذهولة،
have any idea?
هل لديك أي فكرة؟
Can you tell the truth?
هل يمكنك أن تقول الحقيقة؟
The truth! Tell the truth!
الحقيقة! قل الحقيقة!
Your eagerness to marry off your daughter...
رغبتك في تزويج ابنتك...
I understand.
أفهم.
But you sent Wang Wan'er to lure me to a hotel
لكنك أرسلت وانغ وان إير لإغرائي بالذهاب إلى فندق
and drug me with incense.
وأخدّرني بالبخور.
That was a rather despicable tactic, wasn't it?
لقد كان هذا تكتيكًا حقيرًا إلى حد ما، أليس كذلك؟
Wang Penghui,
وانغ بينجوي
the Chen family values integrity and character above all.
تقدر عائلة تشين النزاهة والشخصية فوق كل شيء.
I advise you
انا انصحك
to discipline your daughter properly.
لتأديب ابنتك بشكل صحيح.
Don't worry, Marshal Chen.
لا تقلق، المارشال تشين.
I've already made that fool kneel in punishment.
لقد جعلت هذا الأحمق يركع بالفعل عقابًا له.
♪The flowers fall low into the dust♪
♪تسقط الزهور منخفضة في الغبار♪
♪Cannot see spring's fragile branches♪
♪لا أستطيع رؤية فروع الربيع الهشة♪
♪Beneath Song City's blooms♪
♪تحت أزهار مدينة سونغ♪
♪I've no longer had a home♪
♪لم يعد لدي منزل♪
♪Magnolia petals fly across the sky♪
♪بتلات الماغنوليا تطير عبر السماء♪
♪Spring and autumn come and go♪
♪الربيع والخريف يأتيان ويذهبان♪
♪People gather and part♪
♪يتجمع الناس ويفترقون♪
♪How brave can one be with no regrets?♪
♪كيف يمكن للإنسان أن يكون شجاعًا دون أن يشعر بالندم؟♪
♪I will paint love and hate in the sky♪
♪سأرسم الحب والكراهية في السماء♪
♪Engraving my love for you♪
♪نقش حبي لك♪
♪I roam through this chaotic world♪
♪أتجول في هذا العالم الفوضوي♪
♪Who will guard me for life?♪
♪من سيحرسني طيلة حياتي؟♪
♪I will turn these years into poems♪
♪سأحول هذه السنوات إلى قصائد♪
♪Waiting for the flowers and full moon♪
♪في انتظار الزهور والقمر♪
♪Love and hate entwine, nothing owed♪
♪الحب والكراهية يتشابكان، لا شيء مستحق♪
♪All will drift away with the wind♪
♪كل شيء سوف ينجرف مع الريح♪